<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Overview on Open Component Model</title><link>https://ocm.software/docs/overview/</link><description>Recent content in Overview on Open Component Model</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>© Copyright 2024, SAP SE and Open Component Model Contributors</copyright><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ocm.software/docs/overview/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About the OCM Project</title><link>https://ocm.software/docs/overview/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ocm.software/docs/overview/about/</guid><description>The Open Component Model (OCM) project provides an open standard for describing software artifacts and lifecycle metadata, with the purpose to securely deliver and deploy software products.</description></item><item><title>Benefits of OCM</title><link>https://ocm.software/docs/overview/benefits-of-ocm/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ocm.software/docs/overview/benefits-of-ocm/</guid><description>In today&amp;rsquo;s cloud era, enterprises still grapple with tools and processes rooted in outdated on-premises and monolithic thinking. Ad-hoc, fragmented toolsets are used across software lifecycle processes, severely impacting the ability to deliver software securely, consistently, and compliantly across cloud, on-prem, hybrid and air-gapped environments.</description></item><item><title>Important Terms</title><link>https://ocm.software/docs/overview/important-terms/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ocm.software/docs/overview/important-terms/</guid><description>As the Open Component Model (OCM) revolves around components, it is essential to establish a common understanding of the fundamental terminology employed throughout this website.</description></item><item><title>Specification</title><link>https://ocm.software/docs/overview/specification/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ocm.software/docs/overview/specification/</guid><description>Where to find the OCM specification The most up-to-date version of the OCM specification offers you a deep insight to all technical details of the Open Component Model and explains all elements the model OCM is based on.</description></item></channel></rss>