<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Overview on Open Component Model</title><link>https://ocm.software/docs/overview/</link><description>Recent content in Overview on Open Component Model</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><copyright>© Copyright 2025, SAP SE and Open Component Model Contributors</copyright><atom:link href="https://ocm.software/docs/overview/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About the OCM Project</title><link>https://ocm.software/docs/overview/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ocm.software/docs/overview/about/</guid><description>&lt;p>The Open Component Model (OCM) is an open standard that enables teams to describe software artifacts and their lifecycle metadata in a consistent, technology-agnostic way. It’s built to support secure, reliable delivery and deployment of software—across cloud, on-prem, hybrid, and even air-gapped environments. By decoupling and streamlining lifecycle processes like compliance checks, security scans, and deployments, OCM helps teams collaborate more effectively and build trust into every step of the software supply chain.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Benefits of OCM</title><link>https://ocm.software/docs/overview/benefits-of-ocm/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ocm.software/docs/overview/benefits-of-ocm/</guid><description>&lt;p>Software development is complex. Most organizations struggle with fragmented tools, complicated workflows, and the challenge of managing software across different environments - cloud, on-premises, hybrid, and even air-gapped networks.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Important Terms</title><link>https://ocm.software/docs/overview/important-terms/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ocm.software/docs/overview/important-terms/</guid><description>&lt;p>As the Open Component Model (OCM) revolves around components, it is essential to establish a common understanding of the fundamental terminology employed throughout this website. The following section provides concise definitions of key terms, laying the groundwork for the documentation and tutorials that follow.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Specification</title><link>https://ocm.software/docs/overview/specification/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ocm.software/docs/overview/specification/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="where-to-find-the-ocm-specification">Where to find the OCM specification&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>The most up-to-date version of the 






&lt;a href="https://github.com/open-component-model/ocm-spec/blob/main/README.md" target="_blank" rel="noopener">OCM specification&lt;/a> offers you a deep insight to all technical details of the Open Component Model and explains all elements the model OCM is based on.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>