<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>get on Open Component Model</title><link>https://ocm.software/docs/cli-reference/get/</link><description>Recent content in get on Open Component Model</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>© Copyright 2024, SAP SE and Open Component Model Contributors</copyright><atom:link href="https://ocm.software/docs/cli-reference/get/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>artifacts</title><link>https://ocm.software/docs/cli-reference/get/artifacts/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ocm.software/docs/cli-reference/get/artifacts/</guid><description>Usage ocm get artifacts [&amp;lt;options&amp;gt;] {&amp;lt;artifact-reference&amp;gt;}Options -a, --attached show attached artifacts -h, --help help for artifacts -o, --output string output mode (JSON, json, tree, wide, yaml) -r, --recursive follow index nesting --repo string repository name or spec -s, --sort stringArray sort fieldsDescription Get lists all artifact versions specified, if only a repository is specified all tagged artifacts are listed.</description></item><item><title>componentversions</title><link>https://ocm.software/docs/cli-reference/get/componentversions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ocm.software/docs/cli-reference/get/componentversions/</guid><description>Usage ocm get componentversions [&amp;lt;options&amp;gt;] {&amp;lt;component-reference&amp;gt;}Options -c, --constraints constraints version constraint -h, --help help for componentversions --latest restrict component versions to latest --lookup stringArray repository name or spec for closure lookup fallback -o, --output string output mode (JSON, json, tree, wide, yaml) -r, --recursive follow component reference nesting --repo string repository name or spec -S, --scheme string schema version -s, --sort stringArray sort fieldsDescription Get lists all component versions specified, if only a component is specified all versions are listed.</description></item><item><title>config</title><link>https://ocm.software/docs/cli-reference/get/config/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ocm.software/docs/cli-reference/get/config/</guid><description>Usage ocm get config &amp;lt;options&amp;gt;Options -h, --help help for config -O, --outfile string output file or directory -o, --output string output mode (JSON, json, yaml)Description Evaluate the command line arguments and all explicitly or implicitly used configuration files and provide a single configuration object.</description></item><item><title>credentials</title><link>https://ocm.software/docs/cli-reference/get/credentials/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ocm.software/docs/cli-reference/get/credentials/</guid><description>Usage ocm get credentials {&amp;lt;consumer property&amp;gt;=&amp;lt;value&amp;gt;}Options -h, --help help for credentials -m, --matcher string matcher type override -s, --sloppy sloppy matching of consumer typeDescription Try to resolve a given consumer specification against the configured credential settings and show the found credential attributes.</description></item><item><title>plugins</title><link>https://ocm.software/docs/cli-reference/get/plugins/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ocm.software/docs/cli-reference/get/plugins/</guid><description>Usage ocm get plugins [&amp;lt;options&amp;gt;] {&amp;lt;plugin name&amp;gt;}Options -h, --help help for plugins -o, --output string output mode (JSON, json, wide, yaml) -s, --sort stringArray sort fieldsDescription Get lists information for all plugins specified, if no plugin is specified all registered ones are listed.</description></item><item><title>pubsub</title><link>https://ocm.software/docs/cli-reference/get/pubsub/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ocm.software/docs/cli-reference/get/pubsub/</guid><description>Usage ocm get pubsub {&amp;lt;ocm repository&amp;gt;}Options -h, --help help for pubsub -o, --output string output mode (JSON, json, yaml) -s, --sort stringArray sort fieldsDescription A repository may be able to store a publish/subscribe specification to propagate the creation or update of component versions.</description></item><item><title>references</title><link>https://ocm.software/docs/cli-reference/get/references/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ocm.software/docs/cli-reference/get/references/</guid><description>Usage ocm get references [&amp;lt;options&amp;gt;] &amp;lt;component&amp;gt; {&amp;lt;name&amp;gt; { &amp;lt;key&amp;gt;=&amp;lt;value&amp;gt; }}Options -c, --constraints constraints version constraint -h, --help help for references --latest restrict component versions to latest --lookup stringArray repository name or spec for closure lookup fallback -o, --output string output mode (JSON, json, tree, wide, yaml) -r, --recursive follow component reference nesting --repo string repository name or spec -s, --sort stringArray sort fieldsDescription Get references of a component version.</description></item><item><title>resources</title><link>https://ocm.software/docs/cli-reference/get/resources/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ocm.software/docs/cli-reference/get/resources/</guid><description>Usage ocm get resources [&amp;lt;options&amp;gt;] &amp;lt;component&amp;gt; {&amp;lt;name&amp;gt; { &amp;lt;key&amp;gt;=&amp;lt;value&amp;gt; }}Options -c, --constraints constraints version constraint -h, --help help for resources --latest restrict component versions to latest --lookup stringArray repository name or spec for closure lookup fallback -o, --output string output mode (JSON, json, tree, treewide, wide, yaml) -r, --recursive follow component reference nesting --repo string repository name or spec -s, --sort stringArray sort fieldsDescription Get resources of a component version.</description></item><item><title>routingslips</title><link>https://ocm.software/docs/cli-reference/get/routingslips/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ocm.software/docs/cli-reference/get/routingslips/</guid><description>Usage ocm get routingslips [&amp;lt;options&amp;gt;] &amp;lt;component&amp;gt; {&amp;lt;name&amp;gt;}Options --all-columns show all table columns -c, --constraints constraints version constraint --fail-on-error fail on validation error -h, --help help for routingslips --latest restrict component versions to latest --lookup stringArray repository name or spec for closure lookup fallback -o, --output string output mode (JSON, json, wide, yaml) --repo string repository name or spec -s, --sort stringArray sort fields -v, --verify verify signatureDescription Get all or the selected routing slips for a component version specification.</description></item><item><title>sources</title><link>https://ocm.software/docs/cli-reference/get/sources/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ocm.software/docs/cli-reference/get/sources/</guid><description>Usage ocm get sources [&amp;lt;options&amp;gt;] &amp;lt;component&amp;gt; {&amp;lt;name&amp;gt; { &amp;lt;key&amp;gt;=&amp;lt;value&amp;gt; }}Options -c, --constraints constraints version constraint -h, --help help for sources --latest restrict component versions to latest --lookup stringArray repository name or spec for closure lookup fallback -o, --output string output mode (JSON, json, tree, wide, yaml) -r, --recursive follow component reference nesting --repo string repository name or spec -s, --sort stringArray sort fieldsDescription Get sources of a component version.</description></item></channel></rss>